Until one day,
I ran into his son eloping with his lover.
I can only blame how much the father and son look alike.
So I
couldn't hold back.
I was stunned at the time.
Having just regained my memory,
I was at a loss.
Who are they?
What did you do?
Lao San.
I remember now.
I thought it was him.
It must be his son.
What should I do? I killed them.
It's fine.
Leave it to me.
Lao San sewed the bodies with red thread
to cover up the marks from my axe,
creating the illusion of the Red Lady's revenge.
Then overnight,
hung it on the intertwined branches at Tongxin Cliff,
making everyone believe
that the vengeful spirit of Hong Niangzi had returned for revenge.
Wu Laosan thought we could get away with it,
but as I remembered everything,
I gradually lost control.
I couldn't suppress the resentment in my heart.
So,
I disguised myself as a servant
and sneaked into the Chen Manor.
Seeing the luxurious life in the Chen Manor,
I became even angrier.
I couldn't think of how to take revenge for a moment,
until
I heard the news that Chen still had descendants.
I decided
to end their bloodline.
Chen Sheng,
you were heartless and unfaithful,
and your son is also a debauchee.
I will not allow the world
to have another pitiful person like me.
Ending your bloodline, Chen Sheng,
means
we are even.
Wu Laosan tried to stop me,
but he was too late.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't control myself.
So,
he decided to repeat his old trick,
making all of this
look like the murders by Hong Niangzi.
I will handle this.
Whatever you do,
don't go home.
Then I'll go to the Marriage Shrine
and wait for you.
You must come.
The third son's behavior
was terrifying in the maid's eyes.
In your eyes,
it was suspicious.
But in my eyes,
it was touching.
Then why did the candlestick
happen to ignite the red string?
I am going to the Matchmaker Shrine.
You must come.
So I waited and waited.
I waited until dawn,
but he never came.
My hair turned white overnight,
only to wait for his dead body.
Lord Su,
Mr. Shen,
you guys are amazing.
You don't believe the story of the Red Lady is true.
The third son
also worried that you would find me.
So
he took the blame for everything on my behalf.
Is anyone there?
Mr. Shen.
Lord Su.
Since you are both here,
please be our witnesses.
Lao San.
For all these years,
we never formally bowed in marriage.
I will make it up to you today.
It's all my fault
for clinging to the wrong person
for so long.
I owe you in this life.
In the next life,
and the life after that,
I will be your wife,
never to be separated.
With the Matchmaker as my witness,
this is my vow.
What could
make a person
do such a thing?
Perhaps
it's because of love.
Hurry! The murderer is inside.
Why didn't you misunderstand me like the rest of them?
Because the first time I saw you,
I knew
a woman so determined and impartial in her investigations
could never be
the shameless person they made you out to be.
Thank you for believing in me.
By the way,
I forgot to ask,
where do you live?
I live at my uncle's house.
Right.
I'll head back to the county office then.
See you tomorrow.
Are you dizzy from exhaustion?
Doesn't the magistrate live over there?
I'm just too tired.
Good night.
Are you returning to the manor, Your Highness?
The Prince of Ling has returned!
You're back.
You must be tired from investigating.
It's fine. I'm not tired.
Is it really appropriate for you
to lower yourself by staying at the county office?
It's fine.
I just arrived anyway.
Working on cases with them
helps me get familiar with the area.
I'm scared of him.
My mother was very formidable in Chang'an.
Having a Prince of Ling in Fangzhou
who cares so deeply for the country and its people
must make the Empress Dowager very happy.
Not at all.
It's all thanks to the county office's efficiency.
Although Lord Su is clever,
investigating cases is dangerous.
Please be careful, Your Highness.
I'm a little tired.
You may all leave.
I made your favorite roast chicken.
No need.
I want to be alone for a while.